<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <title>Techno Overfload</title>
    <link href="https://technooverfload.me/feed.xml" rel="self" />
    <link href="https://technooverfload.me" />
    <updated>2022-09-15T01:43:16+01:00</updated>
    <author>
        <name>Techno</name>
    </author>
    <id>https://technooverfload.me</id>

    <entry>
        <title>Synthwave Sanctuary by Super Sonic Con - NCS - Synthwave - Free Music - Retrowave</title>
        <author>
            <name>Techno</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://technooverfload.me/synthwave-sanctuary-by-super-sonic-con-ncs-synthwave-free-music-retrowave/"/>
        <id>https://technooverfload.me/synthwave-sanctuary-by-super-sonic-con-ncs-synthwave-free-music-retrowave/</id>
            <category term="Super Sonic Con "/>
            <category term="Music"/>

        <updated>2022-09-15T01:43:16+01:00</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                        <img src="https://technooverfload.me/media/posts/323/n-Sanctuary-by-Super-Sonic-Con-thumbnail.jpg" alt="" />
                    Music Name : XBRO — Synthwave Sanctuary Author : Super Sonic Con SoundCloud Author Words : "Sky Sanctuary Zone from Sonic 3 &amp; Knuckles XBRO: ️vk.com/xbro_music " Background Image Author : Clubfungus If you liked this music please support the Author. Copyright Notice: All rights reserved to&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                    <img src="https://technooverfload.me/media/posts/323/n-Sanctuary-by-Super-Sonic-Con-thumbnail.jpg" alt="" />
                <figure class="post__video"><iframe loading="lazy" width="560" height="314" src="https://www.youtube-nocookie.com/embed/tap8T3UQV7Q" allowfullscreen="allowfullscreen" data-mce-fragment="1"></iframe></figure>
<p>Music Name : <a href="https://cutt.ly/6C09S0V">XBRO — Synthwave Sanctuary</a></p>
<p>Author : Super Sonic Con <br><a href="https://cutt.ly/BC09SZ8">SoundCloud</a></p>
<p>Author Words :<br>"Sky Sanctuary Zone from Sonic 3 &amp; Knuckles</p>
<p>XBRO: ️vk.com/xbro_music "</p>
<p>Background Image Author : <a href="https://pixabay.com/users/clubfungus-2411039/">Clubfungus</a></p>
<p>If you liked this music please support the Author. Copyright Notice: All rights reserved to the artists mentioned.</p>
<p>XBRO — Synthwave Sanctuary By Super Sonic Con is licensed under a Creative Commons License.<a href="http://creativecommons.org/licenses/by-sa/3.0/">cc-by-sa</a></p>
<p>I do not own any of this music or image, if there is any problem with the video please notify me</p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Contact</title>
        <author>
            <name>Techno</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://technooverfload.me/contact/"/>
        <id>https://technooverfload.me/contact/</id>

        <updated>2022-09-15T01:25:41+01:00</updated>
            <summary></summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                <p>
<script src="https://www.cognitoforms.com/f/seamless.js" data-key="FJy_qoJDDEqFQERDXKoaGw" data-form="1"></script>
</p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Privacy Policy</title>
        <author>
            <name>Techno</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://technooverfload.me/privacy-policy-2/"/>
        <id>https://technooverfload.me/privacy-policy-2/</id>

        <updated>2022-09-15T00:39:23+01:00</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                    TechnoOverlfload Me (“us”, “we”, or “our”) operates the TechnoOverlfload Me website (the “Service”). This page informs you of our policies regarding the collection, use and disclosure of Personal Information when you use our Service. We will not use or share your information with anyone except&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                <p>TechnoOverlfload Me (“us”, “we”, or “our”) operates the TechnoOverlfload Me website (the “Service”).</p>
<p>This page informs you of our policies regarding the collection, use and disclosure of Personal Information when you use our Service.</p>
<p>We will not use or share your information with anyone except as described in this Privacy Policy.</p>
<p>We use your Personal Information for providing and improving the Service. By using the Service, you agree to the collection and use of information in accordance with this policy. Unless otherwise defined in this Privacy Policy, terms used in this Privacy Policy have the same meanings as in our Terms and Conditions, accessible at https://technooverfload.me</p>
<h2>Information Collection And Use</h2>
<p>While using our Service, we may ask you to provide us with certain personally identifiable information that can be used to contact or identify you. Personally identifiable information (“Personal Information”) may include, but is not limited to:</p>
<ul>
<li>Name</li>
<li>Email address</li>
</ul>
<h2>Log Data</h2>
<p>We collect information that your browser sends whenever you visit our Service (“Log Data”). This Log Data may include information such as your computer’s Internet Protocol (“IP”) address, browser type, browser version, the pages of our Service that you visit, the time and date of your visit, the time spent on those pages and other statistics.</p>
<h2>Google AdSense &amp; DoubleClick Cookie</h2>
<p>Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on our Service.</p>
<h2>Cookies</h2>
<p>Cookies are files with small amount of data, which may include an anonymous unique identifier. Cookies are sent to your browser from a web site and stored on your computer’s hard drive.</p>
<p>We use “cookies” to collect information. You can instruct your browser to refuse all cookies or to indicate when a cookie is being sent. However, if you do not accept cookies, you may not be able to use some portions of our Service.</p>
<h2>Service Providers</h2>
<p>We may employ third party companies and individuals to facilitate our Service, to provide the Service on our behalf, to perform Service-related services or to assist us in analyzing how our Service is used.</p>
<p>These third parties have access to your Personal Information only to perform these tasks on our behalf and are obligated not to disclose or use it for any other purpose.</p>
<h2>Security</h2>
<p>The security of your Personal Information is important to us, but remember that no method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage is 100% secure. While we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your Personal Information, we cannot guarantee its absolute security.</p>
<h2>Links To Other Sites</h2>
<p>Our Service may contain links to other sites that are not operated by us. If you click on a third party link, you will be directed to that third party’s site. We strongly advise you to review the Privacy Policy of every site you visit.</p>
<p>We have no control over, and assume no responsibility for the content, privacy policies or practices of any third party sites or services.</p>
<h2>Children’s Privacy</h2>
<p>Our Service does not address anyone under the age of 18 (“Children”).</p>
<p>We do not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from children under 18. If you are a parent or guardian and you are aware that your child has provided us with Personal Information, please contact us. If we discover that a child under 18 has provided us with Personal Information, we will delete such information from our servers immediately.</p>
<h2>Compliance With Laws</h2>
<p>We will disclose your Personal Information where required to do so by law or subpoena.</p>
<h2>Changes To This Privacy Policy</h2>
<p>We may update our Privacy Policy from time to time. We will notify you of any changes by posting the new Privacy Policy on this page.</p>
<p>You are advised to review this Privacy Policy periodically for any changes. Changes to this Privacy Policy are effective when they are posted on this page.</p>
<h2>Contact Us</h2>
<p>If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, please contact us.</p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Terms and Conditions</title>
        <author>
            <name>Techno</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://technooverfload.me/terms-and-conditions/"/>
        <id>https://technooverfload.me/terms-and-conditions/</id>

        <updated>2022-09-15T00:37:59+01:00</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                    Please read these Terms of Use (“Terms”, “Terms of Use”) carefully before using the https://technooverfload.me website (the “Service”) operated by TechnoOverlfload Me (“us”, “we”, or “our”). Your access to and use of the Service is conditioned on your acceptance of and compliance with these Terms.
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                <p>Please read these Terms of Use (“Terms”, “Terms of Use”) carefully before using the https://technooverfload.me website (the “Service”) operated by TechnoOverlfload Me (“us”, “we”, or “our”).</p>
<p>Your access to and use of the Service is conditioned on your acceptance of and compliance with these Terms. These Terms apply to all visitors, users and others who access or use the Service.</p>
<div class="google-auto-placed ap_container"><ins class="adsbygoogle adsbygoogle-noablate" data-ad-format="auto" data-ad-client="ca-pub-0335540293673143" data-adsbygoogle-status="done" data-ad-status="unfilled">
<div id="aswift_2_host" tabindex="0" title="Advertisement" aria-label="Advertisement"><div class="post__iframe"><iframe loading="lazy" width="713" height="0" id="aswift_2" name="aswift_2" sandbox="allow-forms allow-popups allow-popups-to-escape-sandbox allow-same-origin allow-scripts allow-top-navigation-by-user-activation" marginwidth="0" marginheight="0" vspace="0" hspace="0" allowtransparency="true" scrolling="no" src="https://googleads.g.doubleclick.net/pagead/ads?client=ca-pub-0335540293673143&amp;output=html&amp;h=280&amp;adk=3587480669&amp;adf=1877645291&amp;pi=t.aa~a.587424925~i.5~rp.4&amp;w=713&amp;fwrn=4&amp;fwrnh=100&amp;lmt=1663198509&amp;num_ads=1&amp;rafmt=1&amp;armr=3&amp;sem=mc&amp;pwprc=7284328539&amp;psa=1&amp;ad_type=text_image&amp;format=713x280&amp;url=https%3A%2F%2Ftechnooverfload.me%2Fwpautoterms%2Fterms-and-conditions%2F&amp;host=ca-host-pub-2644536267352236&amp;fwr=0&amp;pra=3&amp;rh=178&amp;rw=712&amp;rpe=1&amp;resp_fmts=3&amp;wgl=1&amp;fa=27&amp;dt=1663198508460&amp;bpp=2&amp;bdt=541&amp;idt=510&amp;shv=r20220912&amp;mjsv=m202209080101&amp;ptt=9&amp;saldr=aa&amp;abxe=1&amp;cookie=ID%3Dd7717e57a2fc0a94-22e4d4e264d300de%3AT%3D1651692641%3ART%3D1651692641%3AS%3DALNI_MZFpHDqHQMMHcnn7j5evEfUlrbDUw&amp;prev_fmts=0x0&amp;nras=2&amp;correlator=4138148623673&amp;frm=20&amp;pv=1&amp;ga_vid=493076709.1651388962&amp;ga_sid=1663198509&amp;ga_hid=542370958&amp;ga_fc=1&amp;u_tz=60&amp;u_his=1&amp;u_h=1080&amp;u_w=1920&amp;u_ah=1032&amp;u_aw=1920&amp;u_cd=24&amp;u_sd=1&amp;adx=351&amp;ady=1101&amp;biw=1704&amp;bih=919&amp;scr_x=0&amp;scr_y=0&amp;eid=44759875%2C44759926%2C44759837%2C44761793%2C42531705&amp;oid=2&amp;pvsid=1646579449713963&amp;tmod=1465621385&amp;nvt=1&amp;ref=https%3A%2F%2Ftechnooverfload.me%2F&amp;eae=0&amp;fc=1408&amp;brdim=-8%2C-8%2C-8%2C-8%2C1920%2C0%2C1936%2C1048%2C1704%2C919&amp;vis=1&amp;rsz=%7C%7Cs%7C&amp;abl=NS&amp;fu=128&amp;bc=31&amp;ifi=3&amp;uci=a!3&amp;btvi=1&amp;fsb=1&amp;xpc=9Lqg1q3oqY&amp;p=https%3A//technooverfload.me&amp;dtd=629" data-google-container-id="a!3" data-google-query-id="CN36t6K5lfoCFVnJ1QodVtgGoA" data-load-complete="true" frameborder="0" data-mce-fragment="1"></iframe></div></div>
</ins></div>
<p>By accessing or using the Service you agree to be bound by these Terms. If you disagree with any part of the terms then you may not access the Service.</p>
<h2>Links To Other Web Sites</h2>
<p>Our Service may contain links to third-party web sites or services that are not owned or controlled by TechnoOverlfload Me.</p>
<p>TechnoOverlfload Me has no control over, and assumes no responsibility for, the content, privacy policies, or practices of any third party web sites or services. You further acknowledge and agree that TechnoOverlfload Me shall not be responsible or liable, directly or indirectly, for any damage or loss caused or alleged to be caused by or in connection with use of or reliance on any such content, goods or services available on or through any such web sites or services.</p>
<div class="google-auto-placed ap_container"><ins class="adsbygoogle adsbygoogle-noablate" data-ad-format="auto" data-ad-client="ca-pub-0335540293673143" data-adsbygoogle-status="done" data-ad-status="unfilled">
<div id="aswift_3_host" tabindex="0" title="Advertisement" aria-label="Advertisement"><div class="post__iframe"><iframe loading="lazy" width="713" height="0" id="aswift_3" name="aswift_3" sandbox="allow-forms allow-popups allow-popups-to-escape-sandbox allow-same-origin allow-scripts allow-top-navigation-by-user-activation" marginwidth="0" marginheight="0" vspace="0" hspace="0" allowtransparency="true" scrolling="no" src="https://googleads.g.doubleclick.net/pagead/ads?client=ca-pub-0335540293673143&amp;output=html&amp;h=280&amp;adk=3587480669&amp;adf=2142729367&amp;pi=t.aa~a.587424925~i.13~rp.4&amp;w=713&amp;fwrn=4&amp;fwrnh=100&amp;lmt=1663198509&amp;num_ads=1&amp;rafmt=1&amp;armr=3&amp;sem=mc&amp;pwprc=7284328539&amp;psa=1&amp;ad_type=text_image&amp;format=713x280&amp;url=https%3A%2F%2Ftechnooverfload.me%2Fwpautoterms%2Fterms-and-conditions%2F&amp;host=ca-host-pub-2644536267352236&amp;fwr=0&amp;pra=3&amp;rh=178&amp;rw=712&amp;rpe=1&amp;resp_fmts=3&amp;wgl=1&amp;fa=27&amp;dt=1663198508460&amp;bpp=1&amp;bdt=540&amp;idt=515&amp;shv=r20220912&amp;mjsv=m202209080101&amp;ptt=9&amp;saldr=aa&amp;abxe=1&amp;cookie=ID%3Dd7717e57a2fc0a94-22e4d4e264d300de%3AT%3D1651692641%3ART%3D1651692641%3AS%3DALNI_MZFpHDqHQMMHcnn7j5evEfUlrbDUw&amp;prev_fmts=0x0%2C713x280&amp;nras=3&amp;correlator=4138148623673&amp;frm=20&amp;pv=1&amp;ga_vid=493076709.1651388962&amp;ga_sid=1663198509&amp;ga_hid=542370958&amp;ga_fc=1&amp;u_tz=60&amp;u_his=1&amp;u_h=1080&amp;u_w=1920&amp;u_ah=1032&amp;u_aw=1920&amp;u_cd=24&amp;u_sd=1&amp;adx=351&amp;ady=1799&amp;biw=1704&amp;bih=919&amp;scr_x=0&amp;scr_y=0&amp;eid=44759875%2C44759926%2C44759837%2C44761793%2C42531705&amp;oid=2&amp;pvsid=1646579449713963&amp;tmod=1465621385&amp;nvt=1&amp;ref=https%3A%2F%2Ftechnooverfload.me%2F&amp;eae=0&amp;fc=1408&amp;brdim=-8%2C-8%2C-8%2C-8%2C1920%2C0%2C1936%2C1048%2C1704%2C919&amp;vis=1&amp;rsz=%7C%7Cs%7C&amp;abl=NS&amp;fu=128&amp;bc=31&amp;ifi=4&amp;uci=a!4&amp;btvi=2&amp;fsb=1&amp;xpc=pDNN00Prhe&amp;p=https%3A//technooverfload.me&amp;dtd=636" data-google-container-id="a!4" data-google-query-id="CIGmuKK5lfoCFQQlBgAd1dALcA" data-load-complete="true" frameborder="0" data-mce-fragment="1"></iframe></div></div>
</ins></div>
<p>We strongly advise you to read the terms and conditions and privacy policies of any third-party web sites or services that you visit.</p>
<h2>Termination</h2>
<p>We may terminate or suspend access to our Service immediately, without prior notice or liability, for any reason whatsoever, including without limitation if you breach the Terms.</p>
<p>All provisions of the Terms which by their nature should survive termination shall survive termination, including, without limitation, ownership provisions, warranty disclaimers, indemnity and limitations of liability.</p>
<h2>Disclaimer</h2>
<p>Your use of the Service is at your sole risk. The Service is provided on an “AS IS” and “AS AVAILABLE” basis. The Service is provided without warranties of any kind, whether express or implied, including, but not limited to, implied warranties of merchantability, fitness for a particular purpose, non-infringement or course of performance.</p>
<h2>Governing Law</h2>
<p>These Terms shall be governed and construed in accordance with the laws of Portugal without regard to its conflict of law provisions.</p>
<p>Our failure to enforce any right or provision of these Terms will not be considered a waiver of those rights. If any provision of these Terms is held to be invalid or unenforceable by a court, the remaining provisions of these Terms will remain in effect. These Terms constitute the entire agreement between us regarding our Service, and supersede and replace any prior agreements we might have between us regarding the Service.</p>
<h2>Changes</h2>
<p>We reserve the right, at our sole discretion, to modify or replace these Terms at any time. If a revision is material we will try to provide at least 15 days notice prior to any new terms taking effect. What constitutes a material change will be determined at our sole discretion.</p>
<p>By continuing to access or use our Service after those revisions become effective, you agree to be bound by the revised terms. If you do not agree to the new terms, please stop using the Service.</p>
<h2>Contact Us</h2>
<p>If you have any questions about these Terms, please contact us.</p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Sunshine by nyx eles - NCS - Synthwave - Free Music - Retrowave</title>
        <author>
            <name>Techno</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://technooverfload.me/sunshine-by-nyx-eles-ncs-synthwave-free-music-retrowave/"/>
        <id>https://technooverfload.me/sunshine-by-nyx-eles-ncs-synthwave-free-music-retrowave/</id>
            <category term="nyx eles"/>
            <category term="Music"/>

        <updated>2022-09-09T22:00:14+01:00</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                        <img src="https://technooverfload.me/media/posts/318/hqdefault.jpg" alt="" />
                    Music Name : Sunshine [OSC161] Author : nyx eles SoundCloud Author Words "My submission for OSC161, the One Synth Challenge for July 2022. All sounds are made with Synth1 by Daichi Laboratory. This track was made with Reaper on Linux. There are 16 instances of&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                    <img src="https://technooverfload.me/media/posts/318/hqdefault.jpg" alt="" />
                <p><!-- wp:embed {"url":"https://youtu.be/QmxDGRwtnA0","type":"video","providerNameSlug":"youtube","responsive":true,"className":"wp-embed-aspect-16-9 wp-has-aspect-ratio"} --></p>
<figure class="wp-block-embed is-type-video is-provider-youtube wp-block-embed-youtube wp-embed-aspect-16-9 wp-has-aspect-ratio">
<div class="wp-block-embed__wrapper">
<figure class="post__video"><iframe loading="lazy" width="701" height="393" style="width: 701px; height: 393px;" src="https://www.youtube-nocookie.com/embed/QmxDGRwtnA0" allowfullscreen="allowfullscreen"></iframe></figure>
</div>
</figure>
<p><!-- /wp:embed --></p>
<p><!-- wp:paragraph --></p>
<p>Music Name : <a href="https://cutt.ly/kCEApmO">Sunshine [OSC161]</a></p>
<p><!-- /wp:paragraph --></p>
<p><!-- wp:paragraph --></p>
<p>Author : nyx eles<br><a href="https://cutt.ly/Cndiw1A">SoundCloud</a></p>
<p><!-- /wp:paragraph --></p>
<p><!-- wp:paragraph --></p>
<p>Author Words<br>"My submission for OSC161, the One Synth Challenge for July 2022.<br>All sounds are made with Synth1 by Daichi Laboratory.</p>
<p><!-- /wp:paragraph --></p>
<p><!-- wp:paragraph --></p>
<p>This track was made with Reaper on Linux. There are 16 instances of Synth1.<br>Other plugins used:</p>
<p><!-- /wp:paragraph --></p>
<p><!-- wp:list --></p>
<ul>
<li>Dragonfly Room</li>
<li>B.Schaffl</li>
<li>TAL Filter 2</li>
<li>Airwindows ToTape6</li>
<li>Luftikus</li>
<li>x42 Digital peak limiter</li>
</ul>
<p><!-- /wp:list --></p>
<p><!-- wp:paragraph --></p>
<p>Cover image was generated with wombo.art<br>"</p>
<p><!-- /wp:paragraph --></p>
<p><!-- wp:paragraph --></p>
<p>Background Image Author : <a href="https://cutt.ly/2CEApkc">5519128</a></p>
<p><!-- /wp:paragraph --></p>
<p><!-- wp:paragraph --></p>
<p>If you liked this music please support the Author.<br>Copyright Notice: All rights reserved to the artists mentioned.</p>
<p><!-- /wp:paragraph --></p>
<p><!-- wp:paragraph --></p>
<p>Sunshine [OSC161] By nyx eles is licensed under a Creative Commons License.<a href="http://creativecommons.org/licenses/by-sa/3.0/">cc-by-sa</a></p>
<p><!-- /wp:paragraph --></p>
<p><!-- wp:paragraph --></p>
<p>I do not own any of this music or image, if there is any problem with the video please notify me</p>
<p><!-- /wp:paragraph --></p>
<p><!-- wp:paragraph --></p>
<p><!-- /wp:paragraph --></p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Alone by lashman - NCS - Synthwave - Free Music - Retrowave</title>
        <author>
            <name>Techno</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://technooverfload.me/alone-by-lashman-ncs-synthwave-free-music-retrowave/"/>
        <id>https://technooverfload.me/alone-by-lashman-ncs-synthwave-free-music-retrowave/</id>
            <category term="lashman"/>
            <category term="Music"/>

        <updated>2022-09-09T22:01:38+01:00</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                        <img src="https://technooverfload.me/media/posts/317/hqdefault.jpg" alt="" />
                    Music Name : Alone Author : lashman SoundCloud Background Image Author : Graehawk If you liked this music please support the Author. Copyright Notice: All rights reserved to the artists mentioned. Alone By lashman is licensed under a Creative Commons License.cc-by I do not own&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                    <img src="https://technooverfload.me/media/posts/317/hqdefault.jpg" alt="" />
                <p><!-- wp:embed {"url":"https://youtu.be/FvbOQEia0uk","type":"video","providerNameSlug":"youtube","responsive":true,"className":"wp-embed-aspect-16-9 wp-has-aspect-ratio"} --></p>
<figure class="wp-block-embed is-type-video is-provider-youtube wp-block-embed-youtube wp-embed-aspect-16-9 wp-has-aspect-ratio">
<div class="wp-block-embed__wrapper">
<figure class="post__video"><iframe loading="lazy" width="697" height="391" style="width: 697px; height: 391px;" src="https://www.youtube-nocookie.com/embed/FvbOQEia0uk" allowfullscreen="allowfullscreen"></iframe></figure>
</div>
</figure>
<p><!-- /wp:embed --></p>
<p><!-- wp:paragraph --></p>
<p>Music Name : <a href="https://cutt.ly/aCtjwhU">Alone</a></p>
<p><!-- /wp:paragraph --></p>
<p><!-- wp:paragraph --></p>
<p>Author : lashman<br><a href="https://cutt.ly/nCtjq52">SoundCloud</a></p>
<p><!-- /wp:paragraph --></p>
<p><!-- wp:paragraph --></p>
<p>Background Image Author : <a href="https://cutt.ly/eCtjwrO">Graehawk</a></p>
<p><!-- /wp:paragraph --></p>
<p><!-- wp:paragraph --></p>
<p>If you liked this music please support the Author.<br>Copyright Notice: All rights reserved to the artists mentioned.</p>
<p><!-- /wp:paragraph --></p>
<p><!-- wp:paragraph --></p>
<p>Alone By lashman is licensed under a Creative Commons License.<a href="http://creativecommons.org/licenses/by/3.0/">cc-by</a></p>
<p><!-- /wp:paragraph --></p>
<p><!-- wp:paragraph --></p>
<p>I do not own any of this music or image, if there is any problem with the video please notify me</p>
<p><!-- /wp:paragraph --></p>
<p><!-- wp:paragraph --></p>
<p><!-- /wp:paragraph --></p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Among Stars by Arnyd - NCS - Synthwave - Free Music - Retrowave</title>
        <author>
            <name>Techno</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://technooverfload.me/among-stars-by-arnyd-ncs-synthwave-free-music-retrowave/"/>
        <id>https://technooverfload.me/among-stars-by-arnyd-ncs-synthwave-free-music-retrowave/</id>
            <category term="Music"/>
            <category term="Arnyd"/>

        <updated>2022-09-11T22:02:14+01:00</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                        <img src="https://technooverfload.me/media/posts/316/hqdefault.jpg" alt="" />
                    Music Name : Among Stars Author : Arnyd Spotify iTunes / Apple Music Deezer Bandcamp | Download Napster Google Play SoundCloud Background Image Author : darksouls1 If you liked this music please support the Author. Copyright Notice: All rights reserved to the artists mentioned. Among&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                    <img src="https://technooverfload.me/media/posts/316/hqdefault.jpg" alt="" />
                <p><!-- wp:embed {"url":"https://youtu.be/t727XPxpNjU"} --></p>
<figure class="wp-block-embed">
<div class="wp-block-embed__wrapper">
<figure class="post__video"><iframe loading="lazy" width="560" height="314" src="https://www.youtube-nocookie.com/embed/t727XPxpNjU" allowfullscreen="allowfullscreen"></iframe></figure>
</div>
</figure>
<p><!-- /wp:embed --></p>
<p><!-- wp:paragraph --></p>
<p>Music Name : <a href="https://cutt.ly/OXJnoHo">Among Stars</a></p>
<p><!-- /wp:paragraph --></p>
<p><!-- wp:paragraph --></p>
<p>Author : Arnyd<br><a href="https://cutt.ly/jnHnSz9">Spotify</a><br><a href="https://cutt.ly/wnHnSO0">iTunes / Apple Music</a><br><a href="https://cutt.ly/ZnHnSPJ">Deezer</a><br><a href="https://cutt.ly/XnHnSZg">Bandcamp | Download</a><br><a href="https://cutt.ly/mnHnSNJ">Napster</a><br><a href="https://cutt.ly/lvZskbD">Google Play</a><br><a href="https://cutt.ly/xnHnS9D">SoundCloud</a></p>
<p><!-- /wp:paragraph --></p>
<p><!-- wp:paragraph --></p>
<p>Background Image Author : <a href="https://pixabay.com/users/darksouls1-2189876/">darksouls1</a></p>
<p><!-- /wp:paragraph --></p>
<p><!-- wp:paragraph --></p>
<p>If you liked this music please support the Author.<br>Copyright Notice: All rights reserved to the artists mentioned.</p>
<p><!-- /wp:paragraph --></p>
<p><!-- wp:paragraph --></p>
<p>Among Stars By Arnyd is licensed under a Creative Commons License.<a href="http://creativecommons.org/licenses/by/3.0/">cc-by</a></p>
<p><!-- /wp:paragraph --></p>
<p><!-- wp:paragraph --></p>
<p>I do not own any of this music or image, if there is any problem with the video please notify me</p>
<p><!-- /wp:paragraph --></p>
<p><!-- wp:paragraph --></p>
<p><!-- /wp:paragraph --></p>
<p><!-- wp:paragraph --></p>
<p><!-- /wp:paragraph --></p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Vector Computronus by Logickin - NCS - Synthwave - Free Music - Retrowave</title>
        <author>
            <name>Techno</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://technooverfload.me/vector-computronus-by-logickin-ncs-synthwave-free-music-retrowave/"/>
        <id>https://technooverfload.me/vector-computronus-by-logickin-ncs-synthwave-free-music-retrowave/</id>
            <category term="Music"/>
            <category term="Logickin"/>

        <updated>2022-09-11T22:01:51+01:00</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                        <img src="https://technooverfload.me/media/posts/315/hqdefault.jpg" alt="" />
                    Music Name : Vector Computronus Author : Logickin Audius YouTube - Logickin Test Lab Odyskreekh Logickin.net SoundCloud Author Words "I was messing around with a new genre, Synthwave! Except for some drum samples, all of the synth are made with SunVox Modules, Enjoy! Don't forget&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                    <img src="https://technooverfload.me/media/posts/315/hqdefault.jpg" alt="" />
                <p><!-- wp:embed {"url":"https://youtu.be/Sr9A6vugnBE","type":"video","providerNameSlug":"youtube","responsive":true,"className":"wp-embed-aspect-16-9 wp-has-aspect-ratio"} --></p>
<figure class="wp-block-embed is-type-video is-provider-youtube wp-block-embed-youtube wp-embed-aspect-16-9 wp-has-aspect-ratio">
<div class="wp-block-embed__wrapper">
<figure class="post__video"><iframe loading="lazy" width="560" height="314" src="https://www.youtube-nocookie.com/embed/Sr9A6vugnBE" allowfullscreen="allowfullscreen"></iframe></figure>
</div>
</figure>
<p><!-- /wp:embed --></p>
<p><!-- wp:paragraph --></p>
<p>Music Name : <a href="https://cutt.ly/yXxhf6W">Vector Computronus</a></p>
<p><!-- /wp:paragraph --></p>
<p><!-- wp:paragraph --></p>
<p>Author : Logickin<br><a href="https://cutt.ly/tXxhunx">Audius</a><br><a href="https://cutt.ly/bXxhuRx">YouTube - Logickin Test Lab</a><br><a href="https://cutt.ly/DXxhuUN">Odyskreekh</a><br><a href="https://cutt.ly/DXxhuSs">Logickin.net</a><br><a href="https://cutt.ly/UXxhuFV">SoundCloud</a></p>
<p><!-- /wp:paragraph --></p>
<p><!-- wp:paragraph --></p>
<p>Author Words<br>"I was messing around with a new genre, Synthwave! Except for some drum samples, all of the synth are made with SunVox Modules, Enjoy!</p>
<p><!-- /wp:paragraph --></p>
<p><!-- wp:paragraph --></p>
<p>Don't forget to check logickin.net!<br>You will know my latest status about my project,<br>You can download some of my modules for your music,<br>and You will learn how to do Logic Process in SunVox!</p>
<p><!-- /wp:paragraph --></p>
<p><!-- wp:paragraph --></p>
<p>And don't forget to check out all other amazing music made by other SunVox Users!<br>soundcloud.com/nightradio/sets/sunvox-music-best-of-july-2022</p>
<p><!-- /wp:paragraph --></p>
<p><!-- wp:paragraph --></p>
<p>*The cover image was not much related to the piece, but I just had fun using inkscape and for the aesthetic of 80s art style.<br>"</p>
<p><!-- /wp:paragraph --></p>
<p><!-- wp:paragraph --></p>
<p>Background Image Author : <a href="https://pixabay.com/users/papafox-7788876/">Papafox</a></p>
<p><!-- /wp:paragraph --></p>
<p><!-- wp:paragraph --></p>
<p>If you liked this music please support the Author.<br>Copyright Notice: All rights reserved to the artists mentioned.</p>
<p><!-- /wp:paragraph --></p>
<p><!-- wp:paragraph --></p>
<p>Vector Computronus By Logickin is licensed under a Creative Commons License.<a href="http://creativecommons.org/licenses/by/3.0/">cc-by</a></p>
<p><!-- /wp:paragraph --></p>
<p><!-- wp:paragraph --></p>
<p>I do not own any of this music or image, if there is any problem with the video please notify me</p>
<p><!-- /wp:paragraph --></p>
<p><!-- wp:paragraph --></p>
<p><!-- /wp:paragraph --></p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>DEVCYGR - Rise of the Robots by gbo.gr.cy - NCS - Synthwave - Free Music - Retrowave</title>
        <author>
            <name>Techno</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://technooverfload.me/devcygr-rise-of-the-robots-by-gbogrcy-ncs-synthwave-free-music-retrowave/"/>
        <id>https://technooverfload.me/devcygr-rise-of-the-robots-by-gbogrcy-ncs-synthwave-free-music-retrowave/</id>
            <category term="gbo.gr.cy"/>
            <category term="Music"/>

        <updated>2022-09-11T22:01:28+01:00</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                        <img src="https://technooverfload.me/media/posts/314/hqdefault.jpg" alt="" />
                    Music Name : DEVCYGR - Rise of the Robots Author : gbo.gr.cy Audius Instagram SoundCloud Author Words "Exclusively made with Synth1, EXD-80 and DSK Darkness Theory! Some effects have been added to the master chain in order to give an analogue 80s vinyl feel. "&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                    <img src="https://technooverfload.me/media/posts/314/hqdefault.jpg" alt="" />
                <p><!-- wp:embed {"url":"https://youtu.be/iT3zQRiwoLw","type":"video","providerNameSlug":"youtube","responsive":true,"className":"wp-embed-aspect-16-9 wp-has-aspect-ratio"} --></p>
<figure class="wp-block-embed is-type-video is-provider-youtube wp-block-embed-youtube wp-embed-aspect-16-9 wp-has-aspect-ratio">
<div class="wp-block-embed__wrapper">
<figure class="post__video"><iframe loading="lazy" width="560" height="314" src="https://www.youtube-nocookie.com/embed/iT3zQRiwoLw" allowfullscreen="allowfullscreen"></iframe></figure>
</div>
</figure>
<p><!-- /wp:embed --></p>
<p><!-- wp:paragraph --></p>
<p>Music Name : <a href="https://cutt.ly/kZ43MhT">DEVCYGR - Rise of the Robots</a></p>
<p><!-- /wp:paragraph --></p>
<p><!-- wp:paragraph --></p>
<p>Author : gbo.gr.cy<br><a href="https://cutt.ly/gZ43N0u">Audius</a><br><a href="https://cutt.ly/fZ43N7k">Instagram</a><br><a href="https://cutt.ly/AZ43Mrg">SoundCloud</a></p>
<p><!-- /wp:paragraph --></p>
<p><!-- wp:paragraph --></p>
<p>Author Words<br>"Exclusively made with Synth1, EXD-80 and DSK Darkness Theory!<br>Some effects have been added to the master chain in order to give an analogue 80s vinyl feel.<br>"</p>
<p><!-- /wp:paragraph --></p>
<p><!-- wp:paragraph --></p>
<p>Background Image Author : <a href="https://cutt.ly/GZ43MyJ">Computerizer</a></p>
<p><!-- /wp:paragraph --></p>
<p><!-- wp:paragraph --></p>
<p>If you liked this music please support the Author.<br>Copyright Notice: All rights reserved to the artists mentioned.</p>
<p><!-- /wp:paragraph --></p>
<p><!-- wp:paragraph --></p>
<p>DEVCYGR - Rise of the Robots By gbo.gr.cy is licensed under a Creative Commons License.<a href="http://creativecommons.org/licenses/by-sa/3.0/">cc-by-sa</a></p>
<p><!-- /wp:paragraph --></p>
<p><!-- wp:paragraph --></p>
<p>I do not own any of this music or image, if there is any problem with the video please notify me</p>
<p><!-- /wp:paragraph --></p>
<p><!-- wp:paragraph --></p>
<p><!-- /wp:paragraph --></p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Frontiers (2nd Edit) by MONIN - NCS - Synthwave - Free Music - Retrowave</title>
        <author>
            <name>Techno</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://technooverfload.me/frontiers-2nd-edit-by-monin-ncs-synthwave-free-music-retrowave/"/>
        <id>https://technooverfload.me/frontiers-2nd-edit-by-monin-ncs-synthwave-free-music-retrowave/</id>
            <category term="Music"/>
            <category term="MONIN"/>

        <updated>2022-09-11T22:01:07+01:00</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                        <img src="https://technooverfload.me/media/posts/313/hqdefault.jpg" alt="" />
                    Music Name : Frontiers (2nd Edit) Author : MONIN Twitter instagram Youtube SoundCloud Author Words "Time to transcend and continue but there were borders which could not be crossed so easily " Background Image Author : Kanenori If you liked this music please support the&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                    <img src="https://technooverfload.me/media/posts/313/hqdefault.jpg" alt="" />
                <p><!-- wp:embed {"url":"https://youtu.be/5mCy0Ju-ZA4","type":"video","providerNameSlug":"youtube","responsive":true,"className":"wp-embed-aspect-16-9 wp-has-aspect-ratio"} --></p>
<figure class="wp-block-embed is-type-video is-provider-youtube wp-block-embed-youtube wp-embed-aspect-16-9 wp-has-aspect-ratio">
<div class="wp-block-embed__wrapper">
<figure class="post__video"><iframe loading="lazy" width="560" height="314" src="https://www.youtube-nocookie.com/embed/5mCy0Ju-ZA4" allowfullscreen="allowfullscreen"></iframe></figure>
</div>
</figure>
<p><!-- /wp:embed --></p>
<p><!-- wp:paragraph --></p>
<p><!-- /wp:paragraph --></p>
<p><!-- wp:paragraph --></p>
<p>Music Name : <a href="https://cutt.ly/sZUCyzk">Frontiers (2nd Edit)</a></p>
<p><!-- /wp:paragraph --></p>
<p><!-- wp:paragraph --></p>
<p>Author : MONIN<br><a href="https://cutt.ly/fx3I1Km">Twitter</a><br><a href="https://cutt.ly/qx3I0qO">instagram</a><br><a href="https://cutt.ly/fmMAu98">Youtube</a><br><a href="https://cutt.ly/vx3I0Qg">SoundCloud</a></p>
<p><!-- /wp:paragraph --></p>
<p><!-- wp:paragraph --></p>
<p>Author Words<br>"Time to transcend and continue but there were borders which could not be crossed so easily<br>"</p>
<p><!-- /wp:paragraph --></p>
<p><!-- wp:paragraph --></p>
<p>Background Image Author : <a href="https://cutt.ly/DZUCyoU">Kanenori</a></p>
<p><!-- /wp:paragraph --></p>
<p><!-- wp:paragraph --></p>
<p>If you liked this music please support the Author.<br>Copyright Notice: All rights reserved to the artists mentioned.</p>
<p><!-- /wp:paragraph --></p>
<p><!-- wp:paragraph --></p>
<p>Frontiers (2nd Edit) By MONIN is licensed under a Creative Commons License.<a href="http://creativecommons.org/licenses/by/3.0/">cc-by</a></p>
<p><!-- /wp:paragraph --></p>
<p><!-- wp:paragraph --></p>
<p>I do not own any of this music or image, if there is any problem with the video please notify me</p>
<p><!-- /wp:paragraph --></p>
<p><!-- wp:paragraph --></p>
<p><!-- /wp:paragraph --></p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
</feed>
